[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Star Trek: Nemesis, Captain Picards clone was Romulan Praetor Shinzon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was considered to play the role of The Old Man in the film A Christmas Story?", "correct_answer": "Jack Nicholson", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Newman", "Robert Redford", "Dennis Hopper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Edgar Allen Poe wrote this famous poem in The Bronx in 1846.", "correct_answer": "Annabel Lee", "incorrect_answers": ["Call Me Ishmal", "Our American War", "Hiawatha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is a latecomer punished in Russian traditions?", "correct_answer": "They are forced to drink a full glass of alcohol.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are seated away from the table.", "They are not allowed to sit.", "They are forbidden to take off their coat."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how much whole milk does it take to make one gallon of ice cream?", "correct_answer": "12 pounds", "incorrect_answers": ["10 pounds", "21.2 pounds", "4.5 pounds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To celebrate the 50th anniversary of the movie The Wizard of Oz, a real pair of ruby slippers were made. What is the cost of the slippers?", "correct_answer": "3 million dollars", "incorrect_answers": ["1 million dollars", "10 million dollars", "5 million dollars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the fishing vessel used in the attempts to catch the great white shark in the movie Jaws?", "correct_answer": "The Orca", "incorrect_answers": ["Shark Catcher", "The Pacific Princess", "The SS Minnow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did Opel open a factory in 1982 for production of the Opel Corsa?", "correct_answer": "Zaragoza, Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["Leuven, Belgium", "Poznan, Poland", "Azambuja, Portugal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which celestial body is also a name of a big American vendor of computers, computer components and software?", "correct_answer": "Sun", "incorrect_answers": ["Venus", "Moon", "Pluto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the following statements concerning black tea is wrong.", "correct_answer": "In Chinese, black tea is known as brown tea.", "incorrect_answers": ["Its flavor is stronger than that of most other teas.", "It is made from heavily oxidized leaves.", "It contains more caffeine than other teas."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many calories does one biscuit from Popeyes have?", "correct_answer": "240", "incorrect_answers": ["220", "260", "280"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Berries are good for the heart.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]